<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Comfort Tours</string>
    <string name="Australia_price1">Embassy fess 9,040/- \nOur services charge 5,000/-</string>
    <string name="dtls"><b> Requirements:</b>\n\n <b>1.</b>Passport Validity minimum 6 month.\n
<b>2.</b>Two copy 35mm X 45 mm-size color picture with white backgrounds (no cap or sunglass)\n
<b>3.</b>Trade license (original and photocopy translated and notarized) as well other relevant business documents.\n
<b>4.</b>TIN or Income Tax Certificate\n
<b>5.</b>Update Bank statement with solvency certificate for the last 12 months(international credit card photocopy if available)\n
<b>6.</b>Office or student ID card copy Leave letter, joining letter, salary slip last 3 months.\n
<b>7.</b>If applicant are Government Service holder then need GEO.\n
<b>8.</b>If applicant are retired person need retirements Document.\n
<b>9.</b>Flight and Hotel reservation.\n
<b>10.</b>All previous passports.\n
<b>11.</b>NID &amp; Birth certificate must be notarized.\n
<b>12.</b>Passport copy and other identifying information for spouse and children(even if they are not traveling)\n\n\n<b>Other supporting document</b>\n\n(a) Tour Program\n(b) Visiting card\n(c)
Marriage certificate\n(d) Birth certificate of children\n(e) Document of
properties\n(f) Blue book photocopy of car if any\n(g) Document of other
income if any\n(h) All documents of financial solvency like FDR/ Share
        business/ other savings/Security Deposit /Cash investment\n\n\n<b>Invitee Documents: if you have an invitation letter.</b>\n
1. Passport Copy\n
2. Visiting Card\n
3. Bank statement and solvency certificate copy\n
4. Utility Bill copy\n
5. Invitation letter with full details of applicant and invitee.\n\n</string>


    <string name="brazil_Dtls">
        1.One (1) photocopy of all pages and original passport bearing at least six (6) months
validity.\n
2.Two (2) photocopies of National ID Card and Birth Certificate Translated &amp; Notarized in
Dhaka City Jurisdiction.\n
3. Two (2) recent photographs, passport size, with white background, up to six (6) months.\n
4. Bank statement of the last six (6) months and Balance/Account Certificate statement.\n  
5. One (1) photocopy and original of credit card or debit card statements for the last three
(3) months.\n
6. Income Tax Certificate Translated &amp; Notarized in Dhaka City Jurisdiction.\n
7. Two (2) photocopies each and original of recently paid utilities bill of the last three (3)
months.\n
8. Original and two (2) photocopies of Police clearance.\n
9. Hotel booking in Brazil.\n
10. Two-way air ticket reservation to Brazil.\n
11. Letter of introduction and declaration of current status with the objectives of the visit.\n
12. Pay order of TK 8,000 in the name of &quot;BRAZILIAN EMBASSY IN DHAKA&quot;; The pay order
need to be from a branch of a bank under Dhaka city jurisdiction having online banking
facilities.\n 
One (1) photocopy of Pay Order.\n
13.Extra: Any invitation letter sent from Brazil must have been notarized in the same
Jurisdiction as of the   Brazilian company or individual.\n
* <b>In case of minors and dependents, proof of kinship with one of the applicants and letter of
        responsibility should also be submitted, among other documents.</b>\n
        <b>PLEASE NOTE THAT</b>
Processing the application may take up to 60 days.\n
The submitting of fake or forged documents / information will imply a ban of 10 years
before the candidate can apply again.\n
Visa fees won’t be refundable to candidates.\n
During the process of the application, other documents may be required.\n
 
<b>(Please make sure that you bring all required documents before submission. Incomplete
    application file is not acceptable)</b>\n
 
The Consular Section of the Embassy is open from 09:30 am to 12:30 pm, from Sunday to
Thursday.

    </string>

    <string name="bhutan">On arrival Visa\nYou just need to purchase air ticket.</string>
    <string name="brunai">\n\n\n\n1. Validity of Passport’s last 7 Months.\n
2. Passport photocopy only information page.\n
3. Two copies of passport size picture.\n
4. Brunei air ticket reservation copy &amp; Hotel reservation copy.\n
5. TIN or Income Tax Certificate (Updated)\n
6. Utility bill copy. Like, Telephone, Electricity or Gash bill Copy.\n
7. Official application for Visa. Should be sill &amp; Sign.\n
8. Company letter head pad.\n
9. Leave letter &amp; NOC letter from office(if job holder).\n
10. Solvency certificate from Bank (For single person TK 2,50,000+ / for family TK 5,00,000+)\n
11. Bank Statement (last 6 Months)\n
12. Trade license photo copy with notary public (Applicable for Businessman)\n
13. Visiting Card / Business Card (2 copy)\n
14. Office ID card / Student ID card (if student) Photo Copy.\n
15. Sponsorship Letter for Family Members\n
16. If businessman (letter head pad 2 copy) for application to embassy.\n
17. Marriage certificate photo copy with notary public (If family and spouse name not mentioned in)</string>

    <string name="china">1. Validity of Passport’s last 7 Months.\n
2. Original Passport.\n
3. Two copies of 33x48 mm size picture.\n
4. TIN or Income Tax Certificate (Updated)\n
5. Company letter head pad.\n
6. Leave letter &amp; NOC letter from office (if job holder).\n
7. Solvency certificate from Bank (For single person TK 2,50,000+ / for family TK 5,00,000+)\n
8. Bank Statement (last 6 Months)\n
9. Trade license photo copy with notary public (Applicable for Businessman)\n
10. Visiting Card / Business Card (2 copy)\n
11. Office ID card / Student ID card (if student) Photo Copy.</string>
</resources>
